{
    "subject": "resource/OneRepublic",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:American_pop_rock_music_groups",
    "human_readable": "OneRepublic is subject to American pop rock music groups.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9624165296554565,
            "question": "Is OneRepublic considered a pop rock band?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.71037358045578,
            "question": "What genre of music is OneRepublic known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6523481607437134,
            "question": "Has OneRepublic collaborated with other artists?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6381432414054871,
            "question": "Who are the members of OneRepublic?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6315699219703674,
            "question": "What are some defining characteristics of OneRepublic's music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5399263501167297,
            "question": "Can you name some popular songs by OneRepublic?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5034777522087097,
            "question": "Has OneRepublic won any awards for their music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40203967690467834,
            "question": "Where does OneRepublic originate from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25138014554977417,
            "question": "What is the name of OneRepublic's debut album?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2092803567647934,
            "question": "When did OneRepublic first gain popularity?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=OneRepublic is subject to American pop rock music groups.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7943_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of OneRepublic's debut album?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7943_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where does OneRepublic originate from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7943_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has OneRepublic won any awards for their music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7943_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7943_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7943_120.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7943_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7943_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7943_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7943_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7943_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7943_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7943_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7943_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in JSON format:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThis indicates that the triple \"OneRepublic is subject to American pop rock music groups\" is indeed supported by the documents, as all the files contain information about OneRepublic being an American pop rock band."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"OneRepublic is an American pop rock music group.\" They mention details such as its formation in Colorado, their genre being described as pop-rock and alternative-rock, and their commercial success within the music industry."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}